const subQuestions = [
    {
        question: '3 - 4',
        answers: [
            '1',
            '0',
            '-1',
            '7'
            ],
        correct: '-1',
        quesionId: '0001'
    },
    {
        question: '200 - 100',
        answers: [
            '300',
            '200',
            '100',
            '560'
            ],
        correct: '100',
        quesionId: '0002'
    },
    {
        question: '15 - 17',
        answers: [
            '32',
            '42',
            '37',
            '-2'
            ],
        correct: '-2',
        quesionId: '0003'
    },
    {
        question: '3 - 2',
        answers: [
            '1',
            '3',
            '2',
            '0'
            ],
        correct: '1',
        quesionId: '0004'
    },
    {
        question: '9 - 5',
        answers: [
            '4',
            '9',
            '5',
            '14'
            ],
        correct: '4',
        quesionId: '0005'
    },
    {
        question: '12 - 7',
        answers: [
            '19',
            '5',
            '6',
            '14'
            ],
        correct: '5',
        quesionId: '0006'
    },
    {
        question: '23 - 3',
        answers: [
            '25',
            '23',
            '20',
            '21'
            ],
        correct: '20',
        quesionId: '0007'
    },
    {
        question: '18 - 9',
        answers: [
            '9',
            '8',
            '18',
            '5'
            ],
        correct: '9',
        quesionId: '0008'
    },
    {
        question: '9 - 9',
        answers: [
            '10',
            '9',
            '18',
            '0'
            ],
        correct: '0',
        quesionId: '0009'
    },
    {
        question: '56 - 46',
        answers: [
            '10',
            '46',
            '23',
            '15'
            ],
        correct: '10',
        quesionId: '0010'
    },
    {
        question: '17 - 3',
        answers: [
            '23',
            '20',
            '17',
            '15'
            ],
        correct: '15',
        quesionId: '0011'
    },
    {
        question: '12 - 0',
        answers: [
            '12',
            '13',
            '0',
            '15'
            ],
        correct: '12',
        quesionId: '0012'
    },
    {
        question: '2,123 - 512',
        answers: [
            '1,596',
            '1,712',
            '1,601',
            '1,611'
            ],
        correct: '1,611',
        quesionId: '0013'
    },
    {
        question: '216 - 123',
        answers: [
            '103',
            '93',
            '96',
            '87'
            ],
        correct: '93',
        quesionId: '0014'
    },
    {
        question: '101 - 11',
        answers: [
            '76',
            '90',
            '100',
            '88'
            ],
        correct: '90',
        quesionId: '0015'
    },
    {
        question: '26 - 100',
        answers: [
            '47',
            '-74',
            '74',
            '0'
            ],
        correct: '-74',
        quesionId: '0016'
    },
    {
        question: '1,211,012 - 12',
        answers: [
            '1,211,000',
            '1,190,011',
            '2,011,012,',
            '1,221,112'
            ],
        correct: '1,211,000',
        quesionId: '0017'
    },
    {
        question: '512 - 256',
        answers: [
            '124',
            '256',
            '612',
            '912'
            ],
        correct: '256',
        quesionId: '0018'
    },
    {
        question: '128 - 11',
        answers: [
            '121',
            '129',
            '120',
            '117'
            ],
        correct: '117',
        quesionId: '0019'
    },
    {
        question: '6 - 3',
        answers: [
            '3',
            '6',
            '9',
            '12'
            ],
        correct: '3',
        quesionId: '0020'
    },
]

export default subQuestions;